Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations?
﻿Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations?
﻿Do you have prior practical work experience in ML / AI / NLP area?
﻿Do you have prior practical work experience in ML / AI / NLP area?
﻿Are you comfortable to work in Python and it's related framework?
﻿Are you comfortable to work in Python and it's related framework?
﻿This is a remote opportunity. Are you comfortable committing to a 6-month duration?
﻿This is a remote opportunity. Are you comfortable committing to a 6-month duration?
